(Fukuko) Kakizaki-kun Eternal Boys Don't Quit NOTE Eternal Boys
That's why I won't be performing live anymore.
Haven't you heard? (Yamanaka) Ah, what do you mean?
What do you mean by quitting?
(Kakizaki) Thank you
Why don't you tell Nikolai and the president and not us?
Revenge live, what should we do?
I'm not going out anymore, don't kid yourself!
(Sanada) I'm home (Asai) Chissu NOTE Sanada
(Kakizaki) Sorry, I have to go to work (Imagawa) Huh?
To Kakizaki, was eternal boy such a light thing?
♬～
what happened? What… what?
Kuuu
Well, I guess you can make more money as a host.
(Ishida) Or maybe Kakizaki-san is popular now that he has a girlfriend.
Ha, I've hated that guy for a long time.
Hey... Mr. Yamanaka, you've been drinking a little too much.
Mr. Kakizaki
You don't care about us.
We were... abandoned.
(cry)
Why didn't you tell those kids?
I just didn't have the timing.
Maybe you're scared?
no…
Something has changed, hasn't it?
Since we've known each other for a long time, I can easily tell if it's a lie.
But even though we've known each other for a long time, lately we've been seeing each other for the first time.
What is your calling?
Kakizaki! you…
Talking in your sleep...
toilet…
I'm going to catch a cold, Kakizaki-san.
“Again”? NOTE AGAIN
good night
Mr. Kakizaki, I wonder if he won't come again? Leave that guy alone.
I don't feel well. Why did you come here?
The president's favorite Kakizaki is no longer there.
I brought you a present.
what? that
Is it really a new song?
(Ishida) Those are good lyrics, yeah, yeah.
feel the love for the group
♬～
Where are you going at this hour?
Where is Kakizaki?
I'll go to the store and ask.
But that store...
♬～
(Host) Welcome. This is my first time...
Yes, we will guide you through the system.
There are 3 plans... It's the cheapest.
Please click here.
(Host) Cheers to Sana-chan's first host club!
(Hosts) Good! Okay, okay...
(Hosts) Gui Gui Gui Gui Okay.
Gui Gui Gui Gui Okay, Gui Gui Gui Gui Okay, Gui Gui
Yes!
Huh, Sana-chan, are you feeling nervous today?
Yes haha, that's cute
Huh... Ah, sorry, I need to go to the bathroom.
Cute What else? (Emi) Other than that, there are also rabbits.
rabbit? Sorry
Yeah, yeah, find it, okay?
But here... did you notice?
(Kakizaki) Hmm, cute (Emi) Hehehe
That's why I put on a bear (Kakizaki) It's true, it's a bear.
(Emi) Yeah, so I made it into a rabbit.
(Kakizaki) That's true, it's cute.
The other day, I went to a really stylish cafe.
I think Emi will love it.
Will you look at it? Wait, what? this
Oh, wait... No, Emi-chan, give it back.
No, no, give it back (Emi) Are there any lyrics?
No, what? Tell me
Besides, you went on a trip recently, right?
(Emi) Eh, how do you know? (Kakizaki) I saw it in Korea.
It looked like a lot of fun (Emi) Yeah?
(Kakizaki) Did you eat a lot? (Emi) I ate a lot.
Sanada…
Thank you for your hard work
Good job
Mr. Kakizaki, do you want to become a lyricist?
Huh? Why didn't you tell me?
Is it a secret because you're the host?
Yeah, I don't have the right to dream.
Because I chose a job that makes my dreams come true.
I see, Kakizaki-san is always cool.
Sorry, I tried to be cool.
I've been lying to everyone all the time
Actually, I don't want to be an idol.
As a lyricist, I would like to produce idols.
But I'm actually a coward because I'm afraid of failing.
It's uncool
sorry…
There's nothing uncool about that, right?
Because what attracts people
I'm sure there's something beyond "still"
Be careful of the angle, isn't it too high? that
Yeah, about this much
Sorry I'm late
What did you come here for now? I'm sorry...
Go home with Kakizaki, I don't want to sing this song
Mr. Yamanaka... these wonderful lyrics
This can only be made by someone who loves Eternal Shonen.
These are sacred lyrics full of love.
I don't want to be tainted by someone who abandoned the group.
Hehehehe
What? Sanada, there's nothing wrong with that.
Yamanaka-san, who do you think wrote these lyrics?
Who must have had such great love...
It's Kakizaki-san (Imagawa/Asai) Yeah!
Sorry for keeping it a secret
I don't want to quit being a forever boy.
Actually, I want to work as a lyricist and produce.
Wow, that's amazing. (Asai) Kakizaki-san, are you a genius?
Please let me know sooner
What about Mr. Yamanaka?
♬～
Okay, but is there a condition?
Finally, go to the last live.
Would you like to sing "Again" with me?
You wrote it, so take responsibility and sing it.
Mr. Yamanaka: Whenever I go to a public bath these days, I find myself singing “Again” all the time.
You... you're tone deaf.
That's too loud (Imagawa) hahahaha
Yamanaka-san, are you really happy?
Okay, let's practice now. Don't be so loud. Don't be tone deaf.
(Asai) Even though the sounds don't match at all, they match.
Manpuku Entertainment is over and Eternal Shonen is disbanded.
Why do people give up so easily?
I don't want to disband, I want to be an idol with everyone.